<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Shapes with Gemini</string>
    <string name="action_go">Go</string>
    <string name="baking_title">Guess the picture with Gemini</string>
    <string name="label_prompt" translatable="false">Prompt</string>
    <string name="prompt_placeholder" translatable="false">Look at this sequence of three shapes. What shape should come as the fourth shape? Explain your reasoning with detailed descriptions of the first shapes. Please tell me if my answer matches your thoughts and explain why.</string>
    <string name="image1_description">Cupcake</string>
    <string name="image2_description">Cookies</string>
    <string name="image3_description">Cake</string>
    <string name="results_placeholder">(Results will appear here)</string>
    <string name="msgStartDrag">(Start Drag Here)</string>
    <string name="baking_description">Look at the three pictures presented below and guess which picture will appear next.</string>
    <string name="prompt_answer">Please enter your answer.</string>
    <string name="label_answer">Your Answer</string>
    <string name="battleship_title">Text BattleShip</string>
    <string name="battleship_description">
        This game is a strategy game between you and me. Place your battleships on the 5x5 table.
        Coordinates are from 0, 0 to 4,4. And you shouldn\'t say that. Like you,
        I plan to place my battleship in a certain place in my mind.
        Now you and I are going to play a game of guessing where it is.
        I tell you the expected position and you only give me a hint as to where it deviates from where you thought it would be.
        This is a game where the first person to find the location you and I were thinking of using the hints wins.
        Questions and answers must be asked alternately.
        You are ready ?</string>
    <string name="answerPrompt" translatable="false">I will tell you my answer.
 But now tell me how wrong my answer was compared to your battleship location.
 Please tell me what you think about the location of my battleship.
 Your answer should only explain the differences between your battleship\'s location and my guess.
 Unless you specify the exact location of the battleship.
 And if you guess the location of my battleship, I will also explain the location of my battleship and other details.
 If my guess is correct on your battleship\'s location, I can tell you that it is correct.
 If my guess is correct, I will tell you that it is also correct.
 Once the coordinates are set they should not be changed until I explain them correctly. If my answer is wrong, please explain the difference from the location you thought and I will try to guess the location of the battleship.
 The guess must be in the range 0,0 to 4,4 so if it\'s outside that range, tell me I\'m wrong.
        You shouldn\'t deploy battleships out of range either.
    </string>
    <string name="comparsion_title">Image Comparison</string>
    <string name="comparsion_description">Could you compare the left and right sides of the picture I am showing and explain the differences?</string>
    <string name="prompt_comparison" translatable="false">I will send you an image with two picture. Please look at this and give me a detailed explanation of the differences between the two picture.</string>
    <string name="update_available">Update Available</string>
    <string name="coloring_title">Coloring Sketch</string>
    <string name="coloring_description">Try coloring and saving the image you create next.</string>
    <string name="prompt_color">Enter Coloring Prompt</string>
    <string name="default_coloring_prompt" translatable="false">Dumbledore and Snape having a conversation in the Great Hall of Hogwarts.</string>
    <string name="beforeTime">Last Request Time:%s</string>
    <string name="coloring_description2">AI requests can only be made at 30-minute intervals.</string>
</resources>